Digital Media Department; Collection ua395
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Digital Media Department2002-2016
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany. Digital Media Department
ua395
12 GB
Digital photography created by the campus photographer that documents the University at Albany, SUNY.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
Most Items in this collection prior to 2012 were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by Mark Schmidt and Paul Miller of the Digital Media Department which is part of the Office of Communication and Marketing.
Most of the pre-2012 images were written to optical media (DVDs and some CD-Rs) by the University Photographer. Most of the images were raw camera files .NEF and .CR2 with altered derivatives created as JPG and a few TIFF files. Prior to accessioning, the archivist converted all raw camera images to JPG format and accepted only the original derivatives and the converted versions of files without derivatives.
Most of the images created after 2012 were downloaded 2015 July 19
Historical Note
The Digital Media Department is part of the Office of Communication and Marketing. They are charged with creating video and still images of the university and major events. Many of these items are created for marketing and other publications.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains still photographs created digitally by the campus photographer.
Arrangement of the Collection
Material from the UAlbanyPhotos website was maintained in its original arrangement. If items were moved the new arrangement was also maintained, so there is the potential for duplication.
Material that was transferred on optical media were matched by job number found in the top level directory. This job number was matched to a database maintained by the University Photographer which included basic descriptions, the ordering department, and timestamps. For Images from 2010-2012, a newer database was used that did not include descriptions. Descriptions for these items came from the directory names that held the images.
The images transferred on optical media were matched by the archivist to the arrangement provided by the UAlbanyPhotos website.
Digital Files; UAlbany Communications & Marketing; State University of New York at Albany. Office of Communication and Marketing
- Academics, 2007 December 5-2016 July 17; 1; 4367
  - Academics, 2007 December 5-2016 July 17; 1.1; 4367
    - Criminal Justice: Graduate Program in Criminal Justice Poster 11 x 17, 2000 October 24; 6.3 MB 10
      Immediate Source of Acquisition
      2016 December 14 17:15:55 Accession: ua395-CsBH9SJr2w5jHtUHPFrooF
      2016 December 14 Imaged from optical media with dd, carved from image with fiwalk and icat, converted all raw to jpg
      2016 December 14 description record extracted from photographer's Microsoft Access database by Job number
    - EOP: 4/18/01 @ 10:30 AM BA 212 classroom digital, 2001 May 1; 30.9 MB 25
    - EOP: 4/18/01 @ 2 PM EOP various situations digital, 2001 May 1; 22.7 MB 19
    - Education: 2/4/02 @ 1:30 PM Husted 167 George Litchford w/ student digital, 2002 February 13; 26.5 MB 21
    - Media and Marketing: 2/19/02 @ 10 AM Accelerator Lab Bill Lanford and Thomas Huthwelker digital, 2002 March 1; 29.7 MB 26
    - Ctr. For Autism and Related Disorders: 3/11/02 @ 6:30 PM East Campus / Sch. Of Pub Health Dr. Mark Durand w/class digital, 2002 March 12; 83.5 MB 34
    - Media and Marketing: 4/12/02 @ 9:15 AM Chem 222 group photo in lab digital, 2002 April 26; 34.2 MB 32
    - Physics: 4/19/02 @ 3 PM PAC - Flutterer Lounge reception and lecture for Wolfgang Ketterle - Nobel Prize in Physics digital, 2002 May 3; 79.6 MB 66
    - Education: 6/5/02 @ 9:30 AM CC Ballroom Digital Divide Conference digital image, 2002 June 19; 63.0 MB 43
    - Public Health: 7/23/02 @ 8 AM Rensselaerville Institute Rensselaerville, NY Team building sessions digital, 2002 August 7; 79.0 MB 40
    - Public Health: 8/13/02 @ 10:30 AM School of Public Health East Campus Community Outreach Retreat digital, 2002 August 28; 21.1 MB 18
    - School of Public Health: various for view book, 2002 September 30; 20.0 MB 13
    - Media and Marketing: 10/24/02 @ 2:30 PM Clifton Park, NY Jennifer Toscano / Online Classroom digital, 2002 November 7; 95.9 MB 36
    - Media and Marketing: 11/21/02 @ 4 PM BA-349 Prof. Peter Ross and Students digital, 2002 December 5; 14.5 MB 13
    - UAIM: 1/16/03 @ 2 PM Shadi Shahedipour's Lab Room Photo digital, 2003 January 28; 244.1 MB 106
    - Outreach: 2/11/03 @ 1 PM Studio / Bio B-11 Prof. John Schmidt w/ faculty and students studio groupings and lab shot, 2003 February 25; 245.6 MB 93
    - Outreach: 2/13/03 @ 8:45 AM Developmental Pediatrics / Latham, NY Gail Landsman w/ doctor and paitients digital, 2003 February 27; 260.5 MB 97
    - Outreach: 2/28/03 @ 12:30 PM East Campus A-wing Rm: 203 Peter Levin and David Strogatz digital, 2003 March 12; 14.3 MB 34
    - Media and Marketing: 3/12/03 @ 3 PM Biology Sloan Foundation Award Recipient: Ing-Nang Wang digital, 2003 March 20; 11.9 MB 33
    - Media and Marketing: 3/12/03 @ 9 AM Physics Susan Lee and Carolyn MacDonald w/grad student digital, 2003 March 24; 14.4 MB 37
    - Media and Marketing: 10/10/03 @ 9 AM SS-116 Catherine Bertini w/ students in classroom digital, 2003 October 22; 104.3 MB 81
    - Media and Marketing: 10/10/03 @ 9 AM SS-116 Catherine Bertini w/ students in classroom digital, 2003 October 22; 104.3 MB 81
    - Education: 11/5/03 @ 1:45 PM ED 212 Dean Susan Phillips w/ faculty in office digital, 2003 November 18; 91.7 MB 64
    - Education: 11/5/03 @ 1:45 PM ED 212 Dean Susan Phillips w/ faculty in office digital, 2003 November 18; 91.7 MB 64
    - Media and Marketing: 12/15/03 @ 3:10 PM Draper 221 Jessica Landin and Lauren Mendolera in Jim Acker's class digital, 2003 December 26; 154.3 MB 44
    - African Studies: 3/11/04 @ 12 Noon BA 119 Dedication Ceremony and reception digital, 2004 March 19; 94.0 MB 82
    - African Studies: 3/11/04 @ 12 Noon BA 119 Dedication Ceremony and reception digital, 2004 March 19; 94.0 MB 82
    - Criminal Justice: photo shoot: 4/29/04 @ 1 PM Draper 219 viewbook photography digital, 2004 May 5; 181.4 MB 127
      2016 December 15 15:47:20 Accession: ua395-DpdVWtrwppUpJur3vAWnBU
      2016 December 15 Imaged from optical media with dd, carved from image with fiwalk and icat, converted all raw to jpg
      2016 December 15 description record extracted from photographer's Microsoft Access database by Job number
    - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 95.5 MB 63
      2016 December 14 description record used original folder name
    - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 145.3 MB 90
    - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 55.4 MB 33
    - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 95.6 MB 59
    - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 95.5 MB 63
    - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 52.2 MB 31
    - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 145.3 MB 90
    - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 55.4 MB 33
    - President: photo session: 5/7/04 @ 3:30 - 6:30 PM CC Ballroom KRH Farewell, 2004 May 8; 95.6 MB 59
    - Media and Marketing: 5/5/04 @ 10:20 PAC 262 Auditioning class finals digital, 2004 May 19; 120.2 MB 28
    - Media and Marketing: 5/5/04 @ 10:20 PAC 262 Auditioning class finals digital, 2004 May 19; 120.2 MB 28
    - Academic Support Services: 10/8/04 @ 2 PM EOP offices Project Excel digital, 2004 July 13; 194.5 MB 127
    - Education: 7/15/04 @ 9:15 AM location TBA STEP program w/ Joe Bowman and Albany City School Children Robotics class digital, 2004 July 28; 216.3 MB 134
    - Education: 7/22/04 @ 11 AM CETL / Science Library NYS Trustees visiting Joe Bowman's STEP program digital, 2004 August 5; 103.8 MB 66
    - Media and Marketing: 9/29/04 @ 3:30 PM East Campus young scientists digital, 2004 October 7; 47.5 MB 31
    - Media and Marketing: 10/5/04 @ 2 PM SS-221 Cheryl Frye and Kassandra Edinger digital, 2004 October 19; 197.3 MB 120
    - Media and Marketing: 10/19/04 @ 3 PM LC-18 Judith Johnson's class / Foundations of Great Ideas student presentations digital, 2004 November 2; 52.0 MB 45
    - Media and Marketing: 10/28/04 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom Pres. Ryan's Fall Faculty Speech digital, 2004 November 3; 51.3 MB 39
    - Education: 11/15/04 @ 10 AM ED-115 portrait: Miriam Raider-Roth digital, 2004 November 18; 89.8 MB 72
    - Criminal Justice: 12/8/04 @ 3:30 PM Standish Room/Science Library Former President Vince O'Leary Booksigning digital, 2004 December 8; 132.0 MB 84
      2016 December 15 09:03:03 Accession: ua395-h592ugDm48SamDdDr4w7TS
    - EOP: 12/21/04 @ 1:30 PM studio, 2004 December 29; 15.3 MB 12
    - Ctr for Women in Gov't & Civil Society: 1/21/05 @ 2:45 PM Draper 105 individual portraits & group shot / Fellows digital, 2005 January 25; 309.4 MB 157
    - Criminal Justice: 4/28/05 @ 12:15 PM Location TBA Criminal Justice Symposium Luncheon digital, 2005 March 30; 188.5 MB 120
    - Criminal Justice: 4/29/05 @ 5 PM Location TBA Criminal Justice Symposium Closing Cocktail Reception digital, 2005 March 30; 177.1 MB 126
    - Media and Marketing: 4/11/05 @ 5:30 PM Alumni House George DeLuca w/ students; graduate exams digital, 2005 April 21; 182.7 MB 75
    - Media and Marketing: 4/14/05 @ 10:30 AM Chem 336 / 335 Christopher Wells digital, 2005 April 25; 49.5 MB 31
    - Media and Marketing: 4/13/05 @ 11:30 AM Pres Office Check presentation: Melanie Hansen digital, 2005 April 26; 24.8 MB 13
    - Media and Marketing: 4/14/05 @ 8:30 AM University Club 141 Washington Ave. Albany, NY Pres Hall speaking digital, 2005 April 26; 67.6 MB 45
    - Media and Marketing: 4/26/05 @ 9:45 AM RACC Pres Hall arriving in hydrogen/electric car to help with spring clean up. Digital, 2005 April 26; 104.4 MB 58
    - Media and Marketing: 4/12/05 @ 4:15 PM LC-12 Pres Hall teaching in Sue Faerman's class digital, 2005 April 26; 33.9 MB 22
    - Media and Marketing: 4/13/05 @ 11:30 AM Pres Office Check presentation: Melanie Hansen digital, 2005 April 26; 24.8 MB 13
    - Media and Marketing: 4/14/05 @ 8:30 AM University Club 141 Washington Ave. Albany, NY Pres Hall speaking digital, 2005 April 26; 67.6 MB 45
    - Media and Marketing: 4/27/05 @ 2:30 PM CC Ballroom President's Speech to Faculty digital, 2005 April 27; 142.6 MB 96
    - Media and Marketing: 4/18/05 @ 3 PM Bio 318 Caro-Beth Stewart and Edgardo Sosa digital, 2005 May 2; 61.1 MB 48
    - Criminal Justice: 6/9/05 @ TBA Science Library / CETL room 2 Piyusha Singh's workshop on crime mapping for police officers digital, 2005 June 22; 46.5 MB 31
    - Public Health: 7/18/05 @ Noon - 4 PM Rensselaerville Institue Rensselaerville, NY Northeast Regional Public Health Leadership Institute digital, 2005 July 19; 287.7 MB 197
    - Biology: 7/14/05 @ 9:30 AM Life Science Bldg - various locations general lab shots digital, 2005 July 28; 234.1 MB 152
    - President: 7/20/05 @ 8:30 AM - 9:30 AM School of Public Health Auditorium - East Campus Integrating Genetics into Public Health and Healthcare digital, 2005 July 29; 84.2 MB 51
    - President: 7/20/05 @ 2:30 PM - 2:45 PM Library LC25 Pre-Freshman Summer Program digital, 2005 July 29; 35.5 MB 23
    - President: 7/26/05 @ 10:30 AM Bruno Cancer Center - East Campus Tour w/Sen. Bruno and Pres. Hall digital, 2005 July 29; 237.6 MB 157
    - Chemistry: 7/27/05 @ 11 AM Chemistry Bldg. Forensics lab shot digital, 2005 August 10; 153.0 MB 103
    - Chemistry: make Tif images/scans of book selections: 19 total, 2005 September 7; 69.2 MB 20
    - Rockefeller College: 11/4/05 @ various times Draper 2nd Fl Career Day / College of Computing and Information and the School of Criminal Justice digital, 2005 September 29; 150.0 MB 121
    - President: 11/8/05 @ 9:30 AM ED 335 Education & Counseling Psychology meeting digital, 2005 November 16; 43.4 MB 16
    - Ctr for Women in Government & Civil Society: 1/13/06 @ 1:15 PM Draper 105 head shots / group shot: 10 - 11 persons, 2006 January 24; 224.1 MB 40
    - Corporate and Foundation Relations: 1/13/06 @ 9:30 AM Cancer Research Center / GenNYsis East Campus various lab shots, 2006 January 26; 429.4 MB 229
    - Chemistry: 2/6/06 @ 11 AM Chemistry TBA various locations for brochure images, 2006 February 13; 430.1 MB 228
    - President: 1/31/06 @ 8:45 AM President's Office President for a Day, 2006 February 13; 61.9 MB 25
    - Media and Marketing: 2/3/06 @ 9:30 AM Downtown Campus President Hall cutting down Sign, 2006 February 13; 45.6 MB 17
    - Ctr for Women in Government: 2/1/06 @ 3 PM Outside Draper Hall on Washington Ave. Liberty Partnership HS students and Univ. Minority Health Disparities project leave for tour of health facilities in Arbor Hill, 2006 February 13; 129.3 MB 17
    - President: President Hall's trip to China 12/05, 2006 February 14; 85.2 MB 40
    - Tom Walker, 2006 March 17; 324.4 MB 147
      2016 December 15 description record used original folder name
    - President: 3/7/06 @ 9 AM GenNYSis Board Room East Campus Board of Visitors, 2006 March 17; 61.0 MB 15
    - Elana Gordis, 2006 March 21; 208.5 MB 99
    - Igor Lednev, 2006 March 23; 104.4 MB 53
    - Lee Bickmore, 2006 March 23; 130.7 MB 62
    - Susan Gauss, 2006 March 24; 115.5 MB 56
    - George Levesque, 2006 March 29; 138.6 MB 58
    - Media and Marketing: various times and locations photos for Undergraduate Research Brochure / Mentoring Program, 2006 March 29; 377.4 MB 183
    - Media and Marketing: 4/5/06 @ 6:15 PM A/S 104 Anthropology class / Guatemala, 2006 April 5; 90.3 MB 38
    - President: 3/22/06 @ 9:30 AM Science Library basement Albany HS student / first day, 2006 April 5; 99.4 MB 49
    - Media and Marketing: 4/28/06 @ 8:30 AM Life Science 2094 and 2:30 PM Life Science 2101 Honors Conference, 2006 May 11; 11.6 MB 6
    - Media and Marketing: 4/28/06 @ 8:30 AM Life Science 2094 and 2:30 PM Life Science 2101 Honors Conference, 2006 May 11; 13.3 MB 7
    - Advancement: 5/25/06 @ 2:30 PM Cancer Center - East Campus various lab shots, 2006 June 13; 286.2 MB 156
    - Public Health: 7/18/06 @ 12:30 PM Rensselaerville Institute Rensselaerville, NY School of Public Health Retreat, 2006 July 24; 283.1 MB 133
    - Provost: 7/19/06 @ 1 PM Science Library Rm 223 portrait: James Anderson, 2006 July 31; 84.2 MB 43
    - Criminal Justice: 7/28/06 @ 2 PM Draper 219 portraits: David Bayley, Janet Stamatel, and Marvin Krohn, 2006 August 9; 140.6 MB 90
    - NERFI: 8/16/06 @ 9:30 AM Bio / Forensics Labs NERFI Brochure / Poster photos, 2006 August 30; 652.2 MB 368
    - School of Criminal Justice: 10/6/06 @ 3:30 pm Empire Commons to Standish Room for Albany Symposium on Crime and Justice., 2006 October 9; 220.2 MB 116
    - Media & Marketing: 9/27/06 @ 12:30 PM Biology 125, 2006 October 10; 90.9 MB 51
    - Media & Marketing: 12/13/06 @ 1 p.m. Advisement Services Center for photo of Whitney Sperrazza and her advisor, Kimberly Kerker., 2006 December 14; 99.4 MB 53
    - Media and Marketing`: 12/6/06 @ 12 Noon Middle Earth Counselilng CTR portrait: Carolyn Ortiz, 2006 December 19; 178.8 MB 89
    - Media & Marketing: 1/8/07 @ 3:45 pm in University Hall Atrium for photo of Chris King for web feature. Photo session: 01/09/07 at 3:30 pm in the Main Library, followed directly by shots of the same group in the Campus Center Food Court., 2007 January 8; 690.8 MB 333
      2016 December 19 Submission Information Package (SIP) created with createSIP.py version 0.1
    - Media & Marketing: 2/7/07 at 11 AM, location TBA for photo of Minjeong Kim for Campus Update., 2007 February 8; 106.4 MB 153
    - Jewish Studies: 5/4/07 @ 12 Noon - 2 p.m. Milne 200 for the 6th Annual Michael J. Hindelang Lecture., 2007 May 4; 23.2 MB 39
    - Media & Marketing: 5/15/07 @ 8:30 - 9:30 AM in the atrium of UNH for photo of Moscow Delegation for Campus Update., 2007 May 15; 48.6 MB 64
    - School of Criminal Justice: 6/12/07 @ 10 AM Draper 105, School of Criminal Justice for photos of faculty members Julie Horney, Diana Mancini, Robert Apel and Shawn Bushway., 2007 June 12; 39.3 MB 103
    - Media & Marketing: Prof. Stamatel and Erin Horan photo for web feature here in UAB 201 on 9/7/07 at 9:30 a.m., 2007 September 21; 49.5 MB 99
    - History: 2 sessions- one is at 9 am on 9/19/07 for Lauire Kozakiewicz (head shot) in the well area, 2nd fl of Ten Broeck and the second is @ 2 p.m. same location for Richard Fogarty, David Hochselder and Kendra Smith-Howard (head shots)., 2007 September 21; 20.8 MB 39
    - Media & Marketing: 11/15/07 from 1:30 - 2:30 at the NYSP Forensic Investigation Center to take a button shot of student Danielle Conklin for home page. Pat is need to art direct., 2007 November 23; 45.4 MB 111
    - Media and Marketing: 11/14/07 @ 2 PM Life Sciences Bldg. Alex Shekhtman's Lab w/ three grad students: Shadakshara Swamy Puttamadappa, Jingjing Xie, and Andres MacDonald Web project, 2007 November 28; 41.0 MB 94
    - Media and Marketing: photo sessiion: 1/25/08 @ 2:30 pm location TBA Dian DeFelice / Fence, 2008 February 7; 39.0 MB 93
    - University Events: 3/6/08, 4 - 6 PM, D'Ambra Auditorium, Life Science Building for Distinguished Professor Lecture and Reception featuring Dr. Joachim Frank. Types of shots: candid shots during the lecture and during the first few minutes of the reception; and a couple of posed group shots of the speakers/honoree., 2008 March 6; 42.3 MB 73
    - School of Public Health: Photo session: 4/7/08 @ 1:00 pm for 2 faculty (Martin Tenniswood and JoEllen Welsh) @ the East Campus, 2008 April 7; 111.5 MB 60
    - Life Science: Photo session: 4/1/08 at 11:30 a.m. with Professor Igor Lednev and student Julianne Nichols at Life Science Research Building for a web story., 2008 April 14; 114.6 MB 60
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/9/08 @ 3 pm for Student News ( shots of the program to use in brochure and news in photos) down in the studio., 2008 April 22; 57.1 MB 108
    - Media & Marketing: Photo session: 4/23/08 at 4:45 pm at D'Ambra Auditorim for the Inaugural forum., 2008 April 23; 20.7 MB 52
    - University Events: Photo session: 4/28/08 from 3:30 - 5:00 for the Burton Lecture in Page Hall on the downtown campus., 2008 April 28; 89.8 MB 188
    - Hindelang Criminal Justice Research Center: Photo session: 5/7/08 from 12:00-2:00 PM for the 7th Annual Michael J. Hindelang Lecture in Richardson 002 on the Downtown Campus., 2008 May 7; 18.5 MB 37
    - Jeff Knox_Cancer Research, 2008 May 29; 50.6 MB 98
    - Train Station_Lab Shots, 2008 June 11; 208.7 MB 390
    - Train Station_Lab Shots, 2008 June 19; 208.7 MB 390
    - School of Public Health Seminars and Reception, 2008 June 19; 63.5 MB 141
    - COAP_Program, 2008 July 1; 35.5 MB 78
    - MBA_JD, 2008 September 13; 77.6 MB 24
    - Summers, Robert, 2008 October 7; 40.2 MB 99
    - Fall Faculty Meeting, 2008 October 17; 8.2 MB 24
    - National Institute of Health (NIH) Day, 2008 October 29; 57.5 MB 108
      2016 December 15 12:53:55 Accession: ua395-wcrP5sADh8JRFM3QsbJSwP
    - Criminal Justice_faculty and students, 2008 November 6; 11.2 MB 13
    - English as a Second Language (ESL) Class, 2008 December 10; 10.9 MB 19
    - Professor Lenart_student, 2009 February 5; 54.5 MB 104
    - Prof. Li Niu with students, 2009 March 27; 125.7 MB 68
    - Suniah Ayub_Carol Whittaker, 2009 April 22; 38.1 MB 82
    - John Forsyth, 2009 April 30; 30.5 MB 49
    - School of Public Health Students, 2009 May 7; 12.8 MB 27
    - Hindelang Lecture, 2009 May 7; 12.8 MB 32
    - Kirsten Davison and Student, 2009 July 9; 25.1 MB 51
    - Meggan Keith, 2009 July 18; 38.0 MB 81
    - SSW_classrooms, 2009 October 27; 305.7 MB 228
    - SSW_classrooms, 2009 October 27; 305.7 MB 228
    - Allan Collins Lecture_SOE, 2009 November 5; 31.8 MB 38
    - Karin Reinhold_Kehe Zhu_math, 2009 November 20; 67.3 MB 78
    - Karen Torrejon, 2010 January 29; 53.4 MB 120
    - Paul Agris, 2010 April 8; 59.1 MB 141
    - DigiGirlz, 2010 April 13; 195.7 MB 220
    - NEPHLI_Commencement2010, 2010 July 13; 69.0 MB 138
    - Molinari_ESMaproom, 2010 July 21; 21.8 MB 52
  - Center for Technology in Gover, 2014 July 15-2016 March 4; 1.2; 92
  - College of Arts and Sciences, 2008 January 16-2016 June 30; 1.3; 1315
    - College of Arts and Sciences, 2008 January 16-2016 June 30; 1.3.1; 1315
      - Ctr for Avanced Technology: 1/23/01 @ 9 AM CESTM new employees digital, 2001 February 6; 98.5 MB 43
      - Music: 3/11/01 @ 6 PM PAC Main Theater photos of orchestra digital, 2001 March 26; 98.1 MB 82
      - University Relations: 3/14/01 @ 4:15 PM CESTM Mike Fanchier and assoc. Digital, 2001 March 29; 20.1 MB 20
      - University Relations: 3/20/01 @ 3 PM CETL Tom Macke, Judy Johnson and Jerry Won (student) digital, 2001 April 12; 13.7 MB 12
      - Women's Studies: 4/4/01 @ 2 pm SS341 informal group shots digital, 2001 April 16; 20.5 MB 15
      - Women's Studies: 4/19/01 @ 11:15 HU-20 (instructor) Grace Mose teaching in the classroom digital image, 2001 May 2; 21.9 MB 19
      - UAIM: 4/23/01 @ 11 AM CESTM press conference print and digital, 2001 May 2; 74.5 MB 61
      - University Relations: 5/8/01 @ 12:45 Humanities 290 David Wills with students (presenting Danish gift) digital, 2001 May 16; 27.7 MB 23
      - CELA Institute: 8/14 @ 11 AM and 8/15 @ 9 AM Alumni House Seminar sessions digital, 2001 August 28; 114.9 MB 97
      - UAIM: 1/15/02 @ 11 AM CESTM new personnel digital, 2002 January 28; 12.6 MB 15
      - NYS Writer's Institute: 3/4/02 @ 6:30 PM NYS Museum - Adirondak Hall reception and lecture digital, 2002 February 1; 87.7 MB 101
      - Media and Marketing: 2/6/02 @ 6 - 8 PM CESTM Entrepenuer of the Year Award - Carl Rosner digital, 2002 February 15; 98.2 MB 79
      - Special Events: 4/30/02 @ 3 -5 PM CESTM reception for Dean Kaloyeros digital, 2002 April 19; 74.7 MB 66
      - Media and Marketing: 4/5/02 @ 10:30 AM CESTM Press Conference: Adirondak Council and EPA w/ Chrisy Todd Whitman digital, 2002 April 19; 116.2 MB 93
      - Media and Marketing: 4/24/02 @ 3:45 PM Humanities 210 EAS Honor Students digital, 2002 May 7; 12.0 MB 11
      - UA Outreach: 6/6/02 @ 9:30 AM CESTM rotunda Albany High School students study Nano Electronics color print, 2002 June 18; 3.4 MB 2
      - Media and Marketing: 7/18/02 @ 10 AM CESTM Press Conference digital, 2002 July 29; 14.8 MB 37
      - Media and Marketing: 8/27/02 @ 3:30 PM New Sculpture Studio Prof. Ed Mayer digital, 2002 September 11; 13.4 MB 20
      - UAIM: 9/23/02 @ 11 AM CESTM (2) new employee portraits digital, 2002 September 18; 46.8 MB 37
      - Special Events: 10/25/02 @ 11 AM - 4 PM College of Arts and Sciences Grand Opening color print, 2002 September 19; 153.7 MB 132
      - President: Power Point Show: Faculty/Staff Address photography: New Dean/ Arts and Science, 2002 October 8; 103.3 MB 45
      - President: 11/21/02 @ 11:30 AM - 12:30 PM CESTM Tokyo Electronics anouncement digital, 2002 December 5; 257.2 MB 112
      - E2TAC: 12/12/02 @ 11 AM CESTM press conf./ Sen. Charles Schumer digital, 2002 December 26; 56.1 MB 39
      - Advancemet: 12/13/02 @ 11AM President's Office check presentation w/ KRH and Mr. LeDuke digital, 2002 December 27; 85.8 MB 35
      - President: 12/16/02 @ 10:30 AM President's Residence interior shots of house / holiday cheer digital, 2002 December 30; 228.1 MB 89